Doraemon's Great Prophecy
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
I'm home!
I'm going out!
It's the Magic Hand of 22nd century.
Doraemon, don't fool around
I wanted to stop you from going out no matter how.
You are going to see Shizuka-chan now, right?
Yup.
She is bored at home alone so she wants you to go to her house to play with her
Well, you sure are informed.
Don't go!
Don't stop me! It's none of your business.
OK, I will let you see what happens if you go out.
See, your future is printed in this photo album.
You got hit on your way to her house.
It took you 1 month to recover.
You are not so smart at the first place and it's getting worse.
Really?
So you'd better stay home all-day today.
Shizuka-chan will be angry
Nobita, Shizuka-chan has called you.
What a problem!
Let me reject her call for you.
Hello!
I am sick.
Can you please let me speak too?
What? Funny Manga and specially-made cake?
Did you reject her call for me?
To tell you the truth, I told her you are on your way to her house.
You fool!
Is it OK for you if I get hit?
Don't worry since I will come with you, let's go.
Cake and Manga awaits you.
What?
Nothing, lets go.
Wait, be careful!
Time TV!
We will be there in 10 seconds.
Run, that's the place where you get hit!
That way was dangerous.
it's OK since we know it now.
How dare you step on my son's toy!
It's kind of accident too.
The danger still lurks us.
Look ahead when you walk.
it might come from behind, watch out!
I told you to watch ahead.
Behind! Ahead!
Next, ahead, behind, next
I can't see all of them at once!
So many cars!
There's no way at all.
Now what?
That's it, we must walk through the buildings.
Sorry to come to bother you.
it's a street over there.
It's tough.
Help!
Here is a car!
It's in the yard.
You entered my private yard! Are you two, thieves?
No, there is a profound reason behind this.
What? Just to avoid a car, you came here.
This house is just right on the corner.
So trucks crash in all the time.
See.
I got it, there is a route that is definitely safe.
Doraemon, why didn't you think of it, earlier?
I could ask you the same thing.
I can't put up with this, I wanna go home.
Too late, you will get hit on our way home.
It must be destiny.
That's it! I wonder why didn't I think of it earlier?
Nobita-kun, it's OK.
Bamboo 'Copter!
Put this on your head.
Why didn't you took it out earlier? It's very handy!
Sorry.
I see Shizuka-chan's house
Shizuka-chan, good afternoon!
Stop it!
Sorry, I was so bored.
So I asked my neighbor's kids to come over to my house.
Aren't you glad, Nobita-kun?
Not at all!
But compared to this photo...
It's nothing really serious, so it's ok.
What?
Well, you are right!